(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-22T22:46:52.770446",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
全世界、激震！
The entire world is shaken!
あの超大作が
That monumental masterpiece...
ついに
...finally...
スクリーンへ！！
...comes to the silver screen!
タイムリミットは24時間
The time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は
The hope of humanity...
4人の「●●●●」に託された
...is entrusted to four [BEEP].
なんだ？ここは！？
What is this place?!
どうして……こんなのひどいよ！
Why... this is too cruel!
私のことはもういい！先にいけ！
Don't worry about me! Go on ahead!
いろは～～～～！！！
Iroha~~~~!!!
お、ふざけんな！
Hey, you've got to be kidding me!
私たちの絆は、永遠！
Our bond is eternal!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
Together, we will save humanity!
絶対に忘れないよ……
I'll never forget you...
自分史上、最高傑作です
This is the greatest masterpiece of my life.
せーの、holoX4周年サイコー！
Ready, go! holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は……この中にいる！
The culprit... is among us!
えぇー！？俺！？
Eeeh?! Me?!
きゃーーーーー！
Kyaaaaa!
これは……
This is...
背後から刀で一振り……
A single slash from behind with a katana...
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Detective-dono, what's the matter?
怪しい
Suspicious.
殺人犯と一緒の場所にいられるか！
Like I can stay in the same place as a murderer!
部屋に戻らせてもらう！
I'm going back to my room!
怪しい
Suspicious.
……ふふふふふ
...fufufufufu.
怪しい
Suspicious.
最初から最後までハラハラドキドキでしたー
It kept me on the edge of my seat from start to finish!
せーの、holoX4周年サイコー！
Ready, go! holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
My name is Hakui Koyori! Just your ordinary high school girl!
ただ一つ人と違うことは、科学が好き……ってところかな？
The only thing different about me is... I love science, I guess?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻ーー！
Oh no! I'm late, I'm late!
きゃー！
Kyaaa!
いったー！
Ouch!
見つけた
Found you.
一緒にいると、なんか安心するでござる！
Being with you somehow makes me feel at ease!
いただきましよー！
I'll take this!
あ、こら！
Ah, hey!
おもしれー女
What an interesting woman.
甘じょっぱさが絶妙でしたー！
The sweet-and-salty balance was exquisite!
せーの、holoX4周年サイコー！
Ready, go! holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた……！holoX4周年を検索しちゃったんですか！！！
Y-You...! Did you search for 'holoX 4th Anniversary'?!!!
決して、検索してはイケナイ。「#SSholoX4周年」
Never search for it. '#SSholoX4thAnniversary'.
"SSholoX4周年"を検索した人間に降りかかる数々の出来事――
The numerous events that befall those who search "SSholoX 4th Anniversary"――
ルイ姉……
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから……
Iroha, it's okay...
いろは？
Iroha?
いろは！
Iroha!
うわあ！
Whoa!
きゃーーー！
Ahhh!
終始鳥肌が立ちっぱなしでしたー
I had goosebumps the entire time!
せーの！
Ready, set...
holoX4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
Six...
Let's go!
あはははは！
Ahahaha!
刮目せよ、我らがholoXを！
Behold, our holoX!
この街に…
To this town...
さあ、始めよう。我らの世界を。
Now, let's begin. Our world.
ラララパッタ パララパッタ
La la la patta, pa ra la patta...
ラララパッタ パララパッタパ
La la la patta, pa ra la patta pa...
ラララパッタ パララパッタ
La la la patta, pa ra la patta...
ラララパッタ パラパッタパラパッタパ
La la la patta, pa ra patta pa ra patta pa!
迷宮なラビリンス
A maze-like labyrinth...
招き招かれた 招待状
An invitation, inviting and being invited...
秘密で秘匿の一次元マンション
A secret, concealed one-dimensional mansion...
ガタガタの戸 あの子あり
A rattling door, that girl is there...
No Way No Getaway
迫る魔術のフォークライ
The approaching magic's folk cry...
交差路に突破口も ドタバタの走馬灯
A breakthrough at the crossroads, a hectic revolving lantern...
エックスに吸い込まれて行くよ
We are getting sucked into the X!
覚悟してござれ！
Prepare yourselves!
右往左往に摩訶不思議な苦痛は
Running left and right, the mysterious pain is...
狂わされたマインドイリュージョン
...a driven-mad mind illusion!
さあ交わす言葉よりピュア
So, purer than any words exchanged...
響け 笑い声
Resound, laughter!
ラララパッタ パララパッタ
La la la patta, pa ra la patta...
ラララパッタ パラパッタパラパッタパ
La la la patta, pa ra patta pa ra patta pa!
みんなで乾杯！
Cheers, everyone!
今宵こそ騒ごう
Let's make some noise tonight!
刺激的な迷宮のラビリンス
A stimulating, maze-like labyrinth...
Ah... Ah... Ah...
ラビリンスに散るシエル
Ciel scattered in the labyrinth... Ah...
恐怖 便 接続のWi-Fi
Fear, sickness, connected Wi-Fi...
お眠り街で最凶ルームだけど
It's the worst room in the sleeping town, but...
片目の回廊は普通にアブノーマル
The one-eyed corridor is normally abnormal...
One Shot One Kill
傑作踊るマリオネット
A masterpiece dancing marionette...
落ちる部屋はダンスマット
The falling room is a dance mat...
ランク外は眼中にないが 落雷あかんくない？
Unranked is out of our sight, but isn't lightning bad?
エックスに吸い込まれて行く
We are getting sucked into the X!
迷える子羊くんたち、お砂糖スパイス、それとピンクな4周年でハイになれるドリンクできたよ！
My lost sheep, with sugar, spice, and a pink 4th anniversary, I made a drink to get you high!
ドクドク飲んでくださいね holoXだけに
Drink it right down, just because of holoX!
さあさあ 皆殿も ノーベーで行こうござる！
Come on, everyone! Let's go without limits!
我が飲んだ！
I drank it!
いや お前が飲むんかい！
Wait, you're the one who drank it?!
じゃあとりあえず
Well then, for now...
カパ〜イ！
Cheers!
暗闇の回廊から流れる
From the corridor of darkness...
帝国の冷笑系へ
...to the empire of cynics...
塗り替えられる今夜
...tonight, which will be repainted...
見果てぬ 笑い声
...endless laughter!
お前たちもな！
You guys too!
ラララパッタ パララパッタ
La la la patta, pa ra la patta...
ラララパッタ パラパッタパラパッタパ
La la la patta, pa ra patta pa ra patta pa!
立ち上がって
Stand up
手を取り合おう
and hold hands.
重なって
Unite together
声を高らかに
and raise your voices high.
ラッパッパ ラララッパッパ
Ra-pa-pa, ra-ra-ra-pa-pa.
荒天の海を越えるため
To cross the stormy seas.
つまり反転
In other words, turn things around
覆したい
and subvert it all.
負けられないから
Because we cannot lose.
スーパーフューチャーパーティーラビリンス
Super Future Party Labyrinth!
バイバイ
Bye-bye!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ということで、
And so,
holoX...
holoX's...
4周年！
4th anniversary!
おめでとう！イェーイ！
Congratulations! Yay!
ありがとう！おめでとう！
Thank you! Congratulations!
はりきっていくぞ！
Let's go all out!
おー！
Yeah!
じゃ、ちょっとね、これからの活動の抱負を...
Now, let's share our aspirations for our future activities...
早いね、ペースが。早いね。
That's quick, the pace is so fast.
ルイちゃんから？
Starting with Lui-chan?
え、私から？聞いてないよ。
What, me first? I wasn't told about this.
どうしようかね。
What should we do?
えーっと、みんなありがとう！
Um, thank you everyone!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
えーっと、どうしようかな。5年目も頑張るぞ、holoX！
Um, let me think. We'll do our best in our 5th year too, holoX!
頑張るぞー！おー！
We'll do our best! Yeah!
はい、じゃ、こよ！
Okay, next is Koyo!
はい！
Yes!
えー、この5年目は4人でもっと団結力をグッと...
In this 5th year, the four of us will strengthen our unity even more...
して、
and...
そろそろ日本征服くらいはしていきたいなと！
I think it's about time we conquer Japan!
日本？確かに。
Japan? That's true.
5年目の節目にいいところね。
It's a good goal for our 5th year milestone.
世界はまだちょっと難しいけど、日本征服頑張ります！
Conquering the world is still a bit hard, but we'll work hard to conquer Japan!
おー！頑張るぞ！
Oh! Let's do it!
はい、いろはし！
Alright, Irohashi!
はい！皆さん...
Yes! Everyone...
ご、ござるの5！
Fi... Five as in Gozaru!
ということで、5年目も元気に健やかに健康に活動...
So, in our 5th year too, we will stay energetic, healthy, and sound...
頑張っていきたいと思います！
and do our absolute best in our activities!
holoX 5年目頑張るぞ！
holoX will do our best in our 5th year!
頑張るぞー！おー！
We'll do our best! Yeah!
じゃあ、私いいですか？
Then, is it my turn?
今年も生き残るぞー！
We will survive this year too!
生き残るね。今年も生き残れたしね。
Survive, indeed. We managed to survive this year too.
生き残れた！偉い偉い！
We survived! Well done!
そして、
And...
来年こそ、5年目こそ、我々の年にするぞー！
Next year, in our 5th year, we will make it our year!
するぞー！
We will!
ちょっと待って、ダサい。ポーズがダサすぎる。
Wait a minute, that's uncool. The poses are way too uncool.
なんでなんで？みんな同じのやってるよ。
Why, why? Everyone is doing the same one.
あ、ささささささはどうでもいいから。
Ah, never mind about that.
ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ！
Hey, everyone, take a look!
ライブステージ！
The live stage!
すごーい！かっこいい！
Amazing! So cool!
holoXの最初の登場からうちらかっこよかったよね？
From holoX's very first entrance, we looked so cool, didn't we?
かっこよかった！
We were so cool!
しかもですね、このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて、
And what's more, this stage isn't just spacious...
色んな仕掛けがありますので！
it has all kinds of gimmicks!
注目して、なんか出てきたりとか、
Watch closely, things might pop up...
出てきたりとか、
or appear...
耳生える？耳はもう生えてる。
Grow ears? Ears have already grown.
そして、上がったり、
And it goes up...
変形したりとか、
or transforms,
合体したりとか！
or even combines!
合体？さすがに無理だろ。
Combine? That's definitely impossible.
合体！できました、こよりさん。
Combine! We did it, Koyori-san.
合体はあるんじゃない？
Maybe there is a combination gimmick?
あったんですけど、
There was one, but...
こよりはそういうの大好きなんだけど、
Koyori loves that kind of stuff,
ちょっとさすがにholoX、予算が少なく...
but unfortunately, holoX's budget was too low...
当たり前じゃん！こよりさん！
Of course it is! Koyori-san!
でもこのステージできたからいいじゃん！ありがとうこよ！
But we got this amazing stage, so it's all good! Thank you, Koyo!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ということで、5年目もholoXの皆さん、ぜひ、
And so, in our 5th year, everyone in holoX...
こんな、こんな我々ですけど、よろしくお願いします。
even though we are like this, please continue to support us.
よろしくお願いします！
Please continue to support us!
そしてここで、お知らせでございます！お知らせだよ！
And now, we have an announcement! Here's an announcement!
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると、
If you join the official Hololive channel membership...
なんと限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので！
you'll get access to exclusive emoji stamps!
ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください！
Please use them in the comments to show your support!
さらに！
Furthermore!
なんと今日からもう一つ、メンバーシップ特典があるらしいんですけども、
It seems there's another membership perk starting today!
なんと、先日発表した新曲「スキデカト」と「プライベートアイズ」の壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
You can also get wallpapers for our recently announced new songs, "Sukidekato" and "Private Eyes"!
えー！欲しい！
Wow! I want them!
うちらも入らなきゃいけないのかな。
I guess we have to join the membership too.
はい、そして本日は何やらライブだけではなく、
Yes! And today, it seems there isn't just a live concert...
お？重要な
Oh? / Some important...
え？重要？情報が、
Wait, important? / Information...
情報が、もりもりもりもり、盛りだくさんらしいので
...is super packed with lots and lots of details!
もりもりもりもり盛りだくさん！本当に？
Lots and lots of details! / Really?
皆さん、最後までちゃんと見ていくように！
So everyone, make sure to watch until the very end!
途中退室禁止です。
Leaving midway is strictly prohibited!
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you for your cooperation!
もりもり？もりのじ？森の図？
Mori-mori? / Forest? / Building a forest?
混ぜて！混ぜてよー！
Let us join in! / Me too!
ちょっと待ってください。何ですか？
Wait a second. What is going on?
早くしないと、みんなに見せらんないから、ライブ！
If we don't hurry, we can't show everyone the concert!
そうですね、はい、早速！早速！
That's right, yes! Let's get right to it!
最初はー
First up is...
はーい！
Yes!
こよちゃんのパートから！
Starting with Koyo-chan's part!
おー！なんだそのポーズ！
Oh! What's with that pose?!
可愛い！可愛い！
So cute! / Cute!
バイバーイ！あ、可愛い！
Bye-bye! / Ah, cute!
いってきまーす！いってらっしゃい！
Here I go! / Have a good run!
見ててね！
Watch me, okay?!
見てるよー！
We're watching!
走って！ほら、急がないと、広いから！
Run! Come on, hurry up! The stage is huge!
急かさないでよ！
Don't rush me!
じゃあ、うちらも行くか。
Well, shall we head out too?
あ、俺たちも？
Ah, us too?
早く、早く！
Hurry, hurry!
行くぞ、早く！
Let's go, hurry!
ラブは揮発性 存在自体マジカル
Love is volatile, its existence itself is magical
調合は未完成 トキメキのケミカル
The compound is incomplete, a heart-throbbing chemical
ん～、なるほど。そんじゃあコレならどうか！
Hmm, I see. Then how about this one?
日進月歩なラボラトリー
An ever-progressing laboratory
怪奇！泡立つ謎のポーション！
Bizarre! A mysterious foaming potion!
混ぜるほどに甘くなるなる
The more you mix it, the sweeter it gets
解析！感情のモーション！
Analyzing! The motion of emotions!
奇跡的に美味しくなれ！
Miraculously, become delicious!
フラスコにハート やべぇラテアート
A heart in the flask, crazy latte art
効果のテスト キミが1号
Testing the effects, you're number one
ほら ぼくをスキになれ
Look, fall in love with me
ちょっとキケンなマゼマゼ
A slightly dangerous mix-mix
どっかーんだ！ケミストリーラブ
It's a "dokaaan"! Chemistry Love
アイマイなキミクロマトグラフィー
An ambiguous "kimi-chromatography"
「変」は「恋」のジェネリック
"Strange" is the generic word for "love"
もっと夢中になれなれ
Fall more and more in love!
すいへーりーべ ぼくのふね！
Sui-hei-ri-be, boku no fune!
キュンって仕留めたい キミの胸
I want to capture your heart with a squeeze
ななまがりしっぷ すくらーくかー！？
Nanamagari ship, Sclark!?
爆ラブ！キミと！ケミストリー！！
Baku-Love! With you! Chemistry!
怪奇！魅惑の甘いエーテル！
Bizarre! Fascinating sweet ether!
融けるくらいドキドキするはず？
You're supposed to get heart-throbbing enough to melt?
えっ！？緑のケムリ吐いてる！？
Huh!? Is it emitting green smoke!?
そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃなーい！
Not that type of heart-throbbing!
けどまぁ、ある意味成功かなっ！？
But well, in a way, is it a success!?
ラブは不溶性 勢い余ってラジカル
Love is insoluble, getting overly radical
調合は試作中 今度のはどーですかっ！？
The compounding is in trial, how is this one!?
うわぁぁーー！！逃……イヤどこいく！？
Whoaaa!! Escape... No, where are you going!?
そんなトライ＆爆破をキミと重ねてく
Piling up such tries and explosions with you
キュートさ目指せバクテリオファージ
Aiming for cuteness, bacteriophage
ラボで夢見る キミの1番
Dreaming in the lab, your number one
中毒症状いかがですか？
How are your addiction symptoms?
ぼくがキミのアンチドート
I am your antidote
どっかーんだ！ケミストリーラブ
It's a "dokaaan"! Chemistry Love
アイマイなキミクロマトグラフィー
An ambiguous "kimi-chromatography"
「変」は「恋」のジェネリック
"Strange" is the generic word for "love"
どんなぼくも観測して？
Observe any version of me, okay?
さぁ！どっかーんだ！キミ＋アイ
Now, it's a "dokaaan"! You + Love
化けまくって爆ぜちゃうシナジー
Chemicalizing and exploding synergy
「キミ」こそが「アイ」のアトミック！
"You" are the very atomic of "love"!
もっと夢中になろなろ！
Let's fall more and more in love!
すいへーりーべ ぼくのふね！
Sui-hei-ri-be, boku no fune!
キュンって仕留めたい キミの胸
I want to capture your heart with a squeeze
ななまがりしっぷ すくらーくかー！？
Nanamagari ship, Sclark!?
爆ラブ！キミと追加検証！
Baku-Love! Additional verification with you!
すいへーりーべ ぼくのふね！
Sui-hei-ri-be, boku no fune!
ぎゅっとして ぼくの胸
Hold me tight, my chest
ななまがりしっぷ すくらーくかー！？
Nanamagari ship, Sclark!?
爆ラブ！キミと！ケミストリー！！
Baku-Love! With you! Chemistry!
実験は！キミと！エターナリー！！
The experiment is! With you! Eternally!
「キミが好き」って この感情に潰されてる
I'm being crushed by this emotion called "I love you"
足りない脳は どちらの方か どうでもいいか、もう
Which one of us has the lacking brain? It doesn't matter anymore
傷付いたって 知らない様ね 責任逃れ
Even if I get hurt, you act like you don't care, avoiding responsibility
私はなんで好きなんだ？って問い出す流れ
Starting to wonder, "Why do I even like you?"
最低になった あの子のほうがいいんだもんね
I've become the worst, but she is better, right?
アタシ 興味ないよ キミなんて
I have no interest in someone like you.
マジ半端ないね 舐めた真似
Seriously, what half-assed, mocking behavior.
ポップでキッチュなこの愛に
In this pop and kitsch love,
壊されりゃいい
I hope it breaks you.
止めどないよ 君の愛を独り占めしたい
It's endless, I want to monopolize your love.
毒だろうがなんだろうが抱きしめてあげたい
Whether it's poison or whatever, I want to embrace you.
ライセンス契約独占のフォーリンラブ
An exclusive licensed contract of falling in love,
逃がさないずっと
I'll never let you go.
「キミが好き」ってこの感情に騙されてる
I'm being deceived by this feeling of "I love you."
大事な方は君か私か決めかねてる
Unable to decide who is more important, you or me,
バカ過ぎる君へ
to you, who are way too foolish.
アタシ 興味ないよ キミなんて
I have no interest in someone like you.
ほら振り回してよ 好きなだけ
Go ahead and lead me on as much as you like.
ロックでVIPなこの愛は
Because this rock and VIP love,
渡さないから
I won't give it to anyone.
バカだよね 色ボケだね
"How stupid," "blinded by love,"
それ見たことかだとかもう
"See? I told you so," and all that.
他愛のない貴方に呪われたまま
Still cursed by your silly self...
いや 興味ないよ キミなんて
No, I have no interest in someone like you.
バカなふりしてあげただけ
I was only pretending to be a fool.
愛と愛をぶつけ合って ぐちゃぐちゃになって
Clashing love against love, turning into a messy jumble,
アタシ 興味ないよ キミなんて
I have no interest in someone like you.
マジ半端ないね 舐めた真似
Seriously, what half-assed, mocking behavior.
ポップでキッチュなこの愛に
In this pop and kitsch love,
壊されりゃいい
I hope it breaks you.
見た目だけじゃワカラナイ
You can't tell just from my appearance.
ワタシのこと可愛いだけと
That I'm just cute...
まさか思っていないよね？
You don't actually think that, do you?
ワタシの真実（ほんと）
My real self...
知っていてほしい
I want you to know it.
予測誤差の範囲と
Within the margin of predicted error,
不測の事態も動じない
I remain unfazed by unforeseen events.
おすましフェイスでいるけど
Though I keep a serious face,
心は常に青白く燃える
my heart is always burning white-hot.
諦めはしない
I won't give up,
媚びたりもしない
nor will I flatter anyone,
ワタシを曲げない
I won't compromise myself.
扱いやすいヤツと思うな
Don't think of me as someone easy to handle.
あまく見ると痛い目みるぞ
If you underestimate me, you'll learn a painful lesson.
それでもときには
Even so, sometimes,
逃げ出してしまいたい
I just want to run away.
そんな衝動に弱音吐きたくなる真夜中（よる）もある//だけど
There are midnight hours when I want to voice my weakness to such impulses.
だけど
But,
ほんの小さな小さな妥協が
even the smallest compromise,
積み重なり重なって動けない
can pile up until I'm unable to move,
大きな大きな可能性失くし
losing huge possibilities,
未来を狭めてしまうから
and narrowing my future.
どんなに暗くても辛くても後悔だけはしない
No matter how dark or painful, I will never regret.
イケてるのは見た目じゃなくて
What's cool isn't how you look,
生きかたなんだ
but how you live.
現実と理想との距離を縮められたとしたとしても
Even if I could bridge the gap between reality and my ideals,
おすましフェイスでいるだけ
I'd just keep my serious face,
何事もなかったかのように
acting as if nothing happened.
立ち止まりはしない
I won't stand still,
後戻りもしない
nor will I turn back,
夢を捨てない
I won't abandon my dreams.
らしいとからしくないとか
Whether it's "like me" or "not like me,"
思いとか決めつけないで全部躱し
Don't jump to conclusions about my feelings, dodge them all.
それでも時には温もりが恋しい
Even so, sometimes I long for warmth.
そんな感情に流されてしまいそうな夜もある
There are nights when I feel like being swept away by such emotions.
こんな甘い甘い言葉だけ求めてしまうような弱さは無い無い
I don't have the weakness to only seek sweet, sweet words.
2回2回経験だって私を強くしてくれたから
Because even a few experiences have made me stronger.
これがこれが私のホント
This, this is the real me!
とっても狭い狭い世界の中だけで終わらせてたらつまらないんだ
It would be boring if I let it end in a very, very small world.
広い広い世界の果てまで駆け抜けて生きていくんだから
Because I will run through to the end of the wide, wide world and live on!
どんなに険しく手こずっても楽しんでやるさ
No matter how steep or difficult it gets, I'll enjoy it!
イケてるものはめちゃくちゃじゃなくて生き方なんだから
Being cool isn't about being crazy, it's a way of life!
はい ちゅーもく
Hey, pay attention!
あれもこれもそれもたぶんタブー
That, this, and that are probably taboos.
わかってんの？
Do you get it?
わかってちょー
Please understand!
わかってんな？
Do you understand?
後悔がベスティ 狭心症キャパシティ
Regret is my bestie, angina pectoris capacity...
ビビりじゃ負けない 比じゃない あげる絶叫ビンタ
Not losing to cowardice, giving a screaming slap!
表面上だけalways漂白してもねぇ保存版
Even if you always bleach just the surface, you know?
痛いの？痛いの？飛んでいけないくらい
Does it hurt? Does it hurt? To the extent it won't fly away.
称賛圧巻毛細胞で
With applause, breathtaking trichocysts.
能ない鷹は爪出しましょう
An incapable hawk should show its claws.
あたし
I...
アナスタシスガール
...am an Anastasis Girl!
不滅量産型女
An immortal mass-produced woman!
だからななななな
So what, what, what, what, what?
いちのさんで dandan dan
One, two, three, step, step, step!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
昨日イジメた罰
Punishment for bullying yesterday.
君はななななな
You are what, what, what, what, what?
地獄へだんだんだんだんだん
To hell, step by step, step by step!
革命 go ride
Revolution go ride!
アナスタシスか
Anastasis...
ガール
...Girl!
お口チャック
Zip your mouth!
君の姉、母、位置、どれ？
Your sister, mother, position, which one?
お口チャック
Zip your mouth!
私だけにしてピエロ
Make me your only clown!
健やかなるときも 健めるときも
Whether in health or in sickness.
センセーショナル
Sensational!
人間らしくあれ
Be human-like!
微々調整が不快
Micro-adjustments are unpleasant.
体温 体温 体温 体温
Body temp, body temp, body temp, body temp.
体温 体温 体
Body temp, body temp, body...
痛いの？痛いの？飛んでいけないならば
Does it hurt? Does it hurt? If it won't fly away...
やっちゃい、やっちゃい、精神論で
Do it, do it, with spiritualism.
目には目を満たしてやりましょう保存版
An eye for an eye, let us satisfy it.
あたし
I...
アナスタシスガール
...am an Anastasis Girl!
ブレイク行動時間保存版
Break time!
だからななななな
So what, what, what, what, what?
いちのさんで dandan dan保存版
One, two, three, step, step, step!
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl!
極めてイカンです
It's extremely regrettable.
君はななななな保存版
You are what, what, what, what, what?
地獄へだんだんだんだんだん保存版
To hell, step by step, step by step!
革命 go ride
Revolution go ride!
アナスタシスか
Anastasis...
ガール
...Girl!
あー あー お願い事した
Ah, ah, I made a wish.
あー あー お願い放っといて
Ah, ah, please leave me alone.
嘘ビジュ 嘘ビジュ
Fake visuals, fake visuals.
汚れとなれの果てが踏み出した 稼働がね
Defilement and ruin have stepped out, operational indeed.
あたし保存版
I...
アナスタシスガール保存版
...am an Anastasis Girl!
不滅量産型女保存版
An immortal mass-produced woman!
だからななななな保存版
So what, what, what, what, what?
いちのさんで dandan dan保存版
One, two, three, step, step, step!
アナスタシスガール保存版
Anastasis Girl!
昨日イジメた罰保存版
Punishment for bullying yesterday.
君はななななな保存版
You are what, what, what, what, what?
地獄へだんだんだんだんだん保存版
To hell, step by step, step by step!
革命 go ride保存版
Revolution go ride!
アナスタシスか保存版
Anastasis...
ガール保存版
...Girl!
すきじゃない！ すきじゃない！ Ah!
I don't like you! I don't like you! Ah!
ラブのレポート 冷めやらぬ感情
A love report, feelings that won't cool down.
バカじゃないの 目を覚まして（ね？）
Are you stupid? Wake up! (Right?)
全然平常心で 興味と関心だらけ！
With absolute composure, yet full of interest!
曝け出してウォンチュ！
Lay it all bare, I want you!
シカト出来なくて困る
I'm in trouble because I can't ignore you.
（無視すんなベイビー）
(Don't ignore me, baby!)
でもたまに構ってあげる
But I'll play with you once in a while.
（癖になっちまう！）
(It'll become a habit!)
絶妙な距離感ゲーム
An exquisite distance game.
近く近づく
Drawing closer and closer...
一生デカく！
Forever huge!
ナンデモ超！大サイズなスキ作りましょう？
Let's make an ultra-oversized "like" out of everything!
それが“ライク”なのか“ラブ”なのか
Is it "like" or is it "love"?
ハタマタ両方なんでは！？
Or could it be both!?
ナシアリ！！ ナシ絶対あんだろう！？
Possible or impossible!? There's definitely a catch!
そしてデカく！
And then, make it huge!
トヤカクデカく！ 言や全部叶うからね！
Anyway, make it huge! Because if we say it, it'll all come true!
結局お前
In the end, you...
“と”居ないと うちも居ないとなんか？ノらないわ！
...if you're not here, and I'm not here... it just doesn't feel right!
一旦一緒にやっていきましょう？
Shall we try doing this together for now?
Ah！ ナンダカンダ
Ah! One way or another...
スキは？
How do we like it?
デカく！
Huge!
スキデカく！
Like it huge!
しばらくお付き合いよろしくなッ
Please stick with us for a while!
スキ！ デカ！ スキ！ デカ！ スキ！ デカ！
Like! Huge! Like! Huge! Like! Huge!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
沢山の感情、みんなに伝えて
Convey all these emotions to everyone.
オレだけに魅せてくれたってイイんだぜ？ イイんだぜ？
You know, it's fine if you show them only to me, okay?
一人特別サービスは出来ません！
I can't give special treatment to just one person!
それでも良いかな？
Is that still okay?
（ごめんね？）
(Sorry!)
もっと知りたい事だらけ
There are so many things I want to know more about.
（ほどほどにして？）
(Keep it within reason, okay?)
でも知らない方が幸せか...？
But maybe ignorance is bliss...?
（どっちかにしてよね！）
(Make up your mind!)
絶妙な距離感ゲーム
An exquisite distance game.
バランス取り合う
Balancing each other out.
一生
For life...
好かず好かれずは辛いから
Because not loving or being loved is painful.
丁度良く塩梅で！
So let's find the perfect balance!
お互いもっと分かり合えたら
If we could understand each other more,
特別になれる？（そうだ！！）
Could we become special? (That's right!!)
いつも通じ合える！（かも？？）
We can always connect! (Maybe??)
この先は想像出来ないけど
I can't imagine what lies ahead, but...
結構イイ感じかも！
It seems like a pretty good feeling!
ギリギリでも良いか！
Is it fine even if it's down to the wire!
そのまま進みます！（オッケー！！）
Let's keep going just like this! (Okay!!)
踏みつけて行きます！（了解！！）
Let's trample over it! (Understood!!)
「ここで今後の我々について話し合っていきたいのだが」
"I'd like us to discuss our future at this point, but..."
「別に要らないでしょ」
"That's not really necessary, is it?"
「いいからほら！ 3, 2, 1」
"Just do it, come on! 3, 2, 1..."
「「レッツゴー」」
""Let's go!""
一生すれ違うふたり...
Two people constantly passing each other by...
おい待て！！
Hey, wait!!
一生デカく！
Forever huge!
ナンデモ超！大サイズなスキ作りましょう？
Let's make an ultra-oversized "like" out of everything!
それが“ライク”なのか“ラブ”なのか
Is it "like" or is it "love"?
ハタマタ両方なんでは！？
Or could it be both!?
ナシアリ！！ ナシ絶対あんだろう！？
Possible or impossible!? There's definitely a catch!
そしてデカく！
And then, make it huge!
トヤカクデカく！ 言や全部叶うからね！
Anyway, make it huge! Because if we say it, it'll all come true!
結局お前
In the end, you...
“と”居ないと うちも居ないとなんか？ノらないわ！
...if you're not here, and I'm not here... it just doesn't feel right!
一旦一緒にやっていきましょう
Let's try doing this together for now.
一生
For life...
ツカかず！ ハナれず！
Not too close! Not too far!
飽きられず！ 丁度良く塩梅で！
And never getting bored! Just the perfect balance!
おまえともっと、くだらない事で笑い合ってイタイ！（感情！！）
I want to laugh with you more over silly things! (My emotions!!)
突き合ってイタイ！（かも？？）
I want to go out with you! (Maybe??)
この先も変わらない関係性を
Let's keep this relationship unchanging into the future...
チョット行き過ぎて！
A little too far!
またチョット前進？後退？
Are we moving forward a bit more? Or backward?
一マス進みます！（ラッキー）
Let's move forward one space! (Lucky!)
三マス戻ります！？（なんでだよ）
We're going back three spaces!? (Why!?)
スキは？
How do we like it?
デカく！
Huge!
スキデカく！
Like it huge!
しばらくお付き合いよろしくなッ
Please stick with us for a while!
不思議な関係お見知りおきを！
Please take note of our mysterious relationship!
Private EyeZ
[Title: Private EyeZ]
超常現象 tenderness
Supernatural phenomenon, tenderness.
行くぜ 東奔西走 time less
Let's go, rushing east and west, timeless.
捨てろ 劣等感
Cast aside your inferiority complex.
ほら 最強じゃん
Look, we're the strongest!
今 焼き付けろ
Burn it into your mind now!
超常現象 tenderness
Supernatural phenomenon, tenderness.
行くぜ 東奔西走 time less
Let's go, rushing east and west, timeless.
我等 名探偵⁑
We are great detectives...
いや 迷探偵！
...or rather, clumsy detectives!
さぁ ba ba ba ba bang!!!
Come on, ba-ba-ba-ba-bang!!!
満月の夜潜り抜けて
Slipping through the night of the full moon,
ビルの隙間でため息 wow
sighing in the gaps between buildings, wow.
星のルーペで探し出して
Search for it with a magnifying glass of stars
深い闇へ誘いざなうの
and guide it into the deep darkness.
逮捕連行 秘密のshowtime
Arrest and custody, our secret showtime!
有言実行 世界を制圧
Actions match words, dominating the world!
オレンジに染まっていくホークアイ
A hawk-eye stained in orange...
c'mon now
君の為に mela mela
For your sake, burning up!
愛を燃やせ me la mela
Burn our love, blazing hot!
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
Ever since that day I swore to protect you,
未来の為に mela mela
for the sake of the future, burning up!
この音にノっちゃえば
If we just ride on this sound,
退屈なんて無縁でしょ サヨナラ
boredom will be a thing of the past. Goodbye!
超常現象 tenderness
Supernatural phenomenon, tenderness.
行くぜ 東奔西走 time less
Let's go, rushing east and west, timeless.
捨てろ 劣等感
Cast aside your inferiority complex.
ほら 最強じゃん
Look, we're the strongest!
今 焼き付けろ
Burn it into your mind now!
超常現象 tenderness
Supernatural phenomenon, tenderness.
行くぜ 東奔西走 time less
Let's go, rushing east and west, timeless.
我等 名探偵⁑
We are great detectives...
いや 迷探偵！
...or rather, clumsy detectives!
さぁ ba ba ba bang!!!
Come on, ba-ba-ba-bang!!!
街灯が照らす欲望の影を
Beneath the shadows of desire lit by streetlights,
忍び足で欺いて wow
we deceive with stealthy steps, wow.
震える手を握りしめよう
Let's hold our trembling hands tight.
大丈夫 心配いらないわ
Don't worry, there's no need to fear.
関わらないわ
I won't get involved...
変化 カモフラ 迷彩 カメレオン
Change, camouflage, tactical chameleon,
忠実な犬 従順なチョコレート
A loyal dog, obedient chocolate.
月と太陽 泡を切り裂いた
The moon and sun sliced through the bubbles.
君のためにメラメラ
Burning hot for you,
魂燃やしてメラメラ
Setting my soul ablaze,
どんなときもこの声を届けたい
I want to deliver this voice to you always.
崖っぷちでもメラメラ
Even on the edge, I'm burning hot,
諦めるには早いわ
It's too early to give up!
恩返し 奇跡のお待ちかね
Returning the favor, awaiting a miracle.
まっさきに 救うわ
I'll rescue you first.
そうさ人生は1回でしょう？
After all, you only live once, right?
後悔なんてお門違い
Regret is completely out of place.
どこにいたって迷子になっちゃっても ぷんぷんです
Even if we get lost wherever we are, I'll pout!
有象無象 人混み分けて
Parting through the chaotic crowd.
電光石火 エスケープ
Lightning-fast escape!
君のためにメラメラ
Burning hot for you,
愛を燃やしてメラメラ
Setting my love ablaze,
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
Since that day I swore to protect you.
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning hot for tomorrow,
鼓動を鳴らしてメラメラ
Pounding with a fiery heartbeat,
退屈なんて無縁でしょう？
Boredom has nothing to do with us, right?
さようなら
So, goodbye!
超常現象 フェノメノン
Supernatural phenomenon...
東奔西走 タイムリミット
Running east and west, time limit!
メラメラと
Flaring up...
揺らめいて
and flickering...
今 火を点けろ
set it on fire now!
超常現象 フェノメノン
Supernatural phenomenon...
東奔西走 タイムリミット
Running east and west, time limit!
メラメラと
Flaring up...
揺らめいて
and flickering...
バババババ
Ba-ba-ba-ba-ba!
ねーねーねー！ねー！
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
うるさい！めっちゃ良かったよねー！
Quiet! That was so good, wasn't it?
めっちゃ楽しかったねー！
It was so much fun!
なんで過去形？めっちゃ良いよね！
Why use the past tense? It's still great!
まだ終わってないからね！
Because it's not over yet!
これから、これからが最高だよねー！
From here on, this is where it gets best!
なーにこれ？なーにこれ？
What's this? What's this?
あ、気づいちゃいました？
Ah, did you notice?
変じゃない、めっちゃカッコいいじゃん！こよが作りました！
It's not weird, it's super cool! Koyo made it!
また！また経費使ったんか！
Again! Did you use the company budget again?!
これがボスの給料カット...
So this is where the boss's pay cut went...
いやいやいや、ボスの給料と同じだからね！
No, no, no, it's the same amount as the boss's pay!
ということで、これは告知用カード！
So, these are announcement cards!
1枚目オープン！
First card, open!
ということで、この流れでグッズ紹介でございますね！
So, moving right along, it's time for the merchandise showcase!
イェーイ！今回はそういう感じね！
Yay! So that's how we're doing it this time!
はい、ということで、じゃあ私からね！いきますよ！
Alright, so let's start with me! Here we go!
はい、holoX活動4周年記念グッズ！
もうどこ見ればいいか分からないw
Yes, the holoX 4th Anniversary Commemorative Merch!
I don't even know where to look, haha!
『Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade』、
今日の18時より販売開始されております！
Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade is now
on sale starting from 6:00 PM today!
それではそれぞれ見ていきましょう！
まずは、プレミアムアクリル色紙！
Now, let's take a look at each item!
First up, the Premium Acrylic Art Board!
今回のキービジュアルを使用したアクリル色紙です！
なんと、複製サインとロゴが箔押しになってて、めっちゃいい感じだよ！
This is an acrylic art board featuring our new key visual!
Amazingly, it features duplicated autographs and a foil-stamped logo!
そして、お次がこちらの、カードスリーブ！
キービジュアルを使ったホロスリーブです！こちらなんと、60枚入り！
And next up is this card sleeve!
It's a holo-sleeve featuring the key visual! And it comes with 60 sleeves!
使いやすいですね！そして...
They're very handy! And next...
アクリルスタンド！
Acrylic Stand!
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで、
ぜひアクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいね！
The expressions are slightly different from the key visual design,
so please compare them with the acrylic art board!
気持ち悪っw 帰りますw
こよとね、いろはも可愛いね！
That's creepy... I'm going home.
Koyo's and Iroha's are super cute too!
そして、こちら！
And here is this!
はい、記念メダルも発売しております！
なんとね、ケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます！
Yes, we are also selling commemorative medals!
These medals actually come with a case and a drawstring pouch!
こちらね、期生ごとでデザインが異なっておりますので、
なんと今回は、holoXだけのデザインになっております！
The design varies depending on the generation,
so this time, it features a holoX-exclusive design!
ぜひぜひゲットして、よーくチェックしてみてください！
なんか騒がしいな！ドリルやめろ、ドリルw
So please get one and check it out!
You guys are being pretty noisy over there! Stop drilling, haha!
はい、ということで、次は2枚目のカード！
カードオープン！
Alright, so next is the second card!
Open!
ということで、タイミーコラボ！
Here it is! Our Timee collaboration!
先日タイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけど、
現地の様子があるということで、見てみましょう！
We recently recruited for some rare part-time jobs on Timee,
and we have footage from the site, so let's take a look!
どん！すごい！
ちゃんとholoXの宣伝をしてる！ありがとうございます！
Ta-da! Amazing! They're actually promoting holoX!
Thank you so much!
他にもありますよ、どん！
おおー！配ってる！
We have more, ta-da!
Ooh! They're handing them out!
なるようになる、なるようにね。
It'll work out. It will, won't it?
でもこれで知ってくれた人もいるよね。
But some people got to know us through this, right?
絶対そう！嬉しい！もう一枚やります、ドン！
Definitely! I'm so glad. Here's one more! Bam!
お、新宿！新宿！
Oh, Shinjuku! Shinjuku!
あれ？後ろのも映ってる？
Wait, is the background in it too?
あれ？あれ？聞いてた？聞いてた？
Wait, wait... Did they tell us about this?
聞いてないよ！今日のあの21時前に流れていた、あのよくわからない...
We weren't told! The one playing before 9:00 PM today, that mysterious...
あのよくわからない...
...that mysterious...
おい！流れてたのかよ！大丈夫か？
Hey! It was playing?! Is it okay?!
あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh?
なんかさ、かっこいいMVとか流したほうがいいのに。
You know, wouldn't it be better to play a cool MV?
ライブ映像とか流したらもっと...
If they played live concert footage, it would be even...
でも、ありがとう！
But, thank you!
ということで、こちら、応募どれぐらい来たと思う？
So, how many applications do you think we got for this?
そう、でもお仕事だからね。お仕事だからやっぱり...
Right, but it's a job. Since it's a job, after all...
100人とか来てくれたら嬉しいよね。
We'd be happy if like 100 people applied.
100人、そう、大変だからね。
100 people, yeah, because it's tough.
なんと！数千人の応募が来ました！
To our surprise, we received several thousand applications!
すごすぎる！ありがとう！
That's incredible! Thank you!
え、驚きすぎ、驚きすぎ。うおおお！
Whoa, that's too much of a surprise, too much. Whoa!
そんなに？！
That many?!
給料もらったおかげで。
Thanks to getting paid.
給料もらったからね、決まってる。
Since they got paid, of course.
あの、いろはちゃんよりも多めに渡しています。
Um, we paid them more than Iroha.
やめて！しっかり口座に。
Stop it! Right into their account.
タイミーさんですからね。
Because it's Timee, after all.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
サンキューのみんなもありがとう。
Thank you to all the quick-laborers, too.
そして次はなんだ？オープン！
And what's next? Open!
来い来い来い！何これ？あ、来た！
Come on, come on! What is this? Oh, here it comes!
じゃじゃーん！タワーコラボだ！
Tada! A tower collaboration!
タワー、タワーということで、皆さん、タワーコラボ情報公開されていますが、こちら！
A tower! Yes, the information about the tower collaboration has been released, and here it is!
全国4ヶ所で行われる、holoXタワーインベージョン！イェーイ！
Held at four locations nationwide: holoX Tower Invasion! Yay!
12月4日から開催されます。
It starts on December 4th.
さっぽろテレビ塔、東京タワー、中部電力 MIRAI TOWER、
It will be held at Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower, Chubu Electric Power MIRAI TOWER,
梅田スカイビルで開催されますので、ぜひ皆さん行ってくださいね！
and Umeda Sky Building, so please check it out!
私たちが、私たちがholoXタワー... おい、待て！
We are... We are the holoX Tower... Hey, wait!
今回は言いたいことがあるんですけど。
We have something we want to say this time...
ちゃんと予約をしないとですね、あの、皆さん入れないんで。
You must make a reservation, otherwise you won't be able to get in.
事前予約必須です。そうなんです、事前予約。
Advance reservation is required. Yes, that's right. Advance reservation...
忘れてる人もいると思うので、その場に行っても入れないらしい。
Because some people might forget. Apparently, you can't enter just by showing up.
ちゃんと、予約をするように！
Make sure to make a reservation!
よろしくお願いします。
Please do so.
よし、帰ろう、帰ろう。次、次、次。
Alright, let's head back. Next, next, next.
ドーン！オープン！はい！
Boom! Open! Yes!
せーの、なんと、なんと！ホロライブの新サービス？
One, two... To our surprise, a new Hololive service?!
あ、新しいサービス！ライブの感動を最速でお届け！
Oh, a new service! Bringing you the excitement of the live concert as fast as possible!
秘密結社holoX、4周年のライブブロマイドが、
Secret Society holoX 4th Anniversary live bromides...
なんと今日のライブの写真が明日からコンビニでプリントアウトできるんだって！
Unbelievably, photos from today's concert can be printed at convenience stores starting tomorrow!
えー！手に入るんだ！そうなんだよ！すごーい！
Eh! We can get them?! That's right! Amazing!
対象店舗は、ファミリーマート、ローソン、
Participating stores are FamilyMart, Lawson,
ミニストップになります。
and Ministop.
そして、今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです。
And apparently, you can pre-order them online starting right now.
ただね、明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら購入することもできるみたいなので、
But starting tomorrow, you can also purchase them at convenience stores while choosing your photos.
詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください。
For details, check out the link in the bottom left.
こっち、こっち、こっち、こっち、この辺。
Over here, here, here, here, around here.
さらにですね、今回はそちらのお写真に、ブロマイドに私たちのメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけれど。
Furthermore, this time, you can add a message from us to those photos—to the bromides.
えー、すごい！今から書くそうです。ええ？！
Eh, amazing! We are going to write them right now. Eh?!
ちょっと待って、見えないから。ここで書くんだ。
Wait a second, we can't see it. We're writing here.
しかも考えてないけど、まあまあまあ...
And we haven't thought of anything yet, but oh well...
何にどうなんの？考えて書いてください。
What is this going to turn into? Please think and write.
はい。え、はい。
Okay. Oh, okay.
全部。何これ？
Everything. What is this?
しかもね、時間も迫ってますからね、早く書いてください。
Also, time is ticking, so write quickly.
にょにょにょ... 意外と集中力...
Nyo nyo nyo... Surprisingly, this takes concentration.
繋げて、繋げて。安牌、安牌で。
Keep talking, keep talking. Let's play it safe.
オッケー、書いた。早くね！
Okay, done. Hurry up!
これ、あ、可愛い。見せて。
This is... oh, cute. Show me.
まあまあ、こよっぽいですね。あ、いいですね。こよっぽい。
Well, this is very Koyo-like. Oh, that's nice. Koyo-like.
いつまで書いてんの？みんな終わった？
How long are you going to keep writing? Is everyone finished?
回収、回収。回収して、みんな出して。お願いいしますね。
Collect, collect. Let's collect them, everyone show them. Please.
ということでこれでお願いします。
So, here you go.
まあ、みんなね、何書いたかすごく気になるとは思うのですが、こちらのメッセージ内容は...
Well, I'm sure everyone is very curious about what we wrote. But the content of these messages is...
みんなが、あの、私が書いたのは... ダメですよ！
The one that I wrote is... No way!
言わないで！みんな買ってからのお楽しみ。ダメに決まってんだろ！
Don't say it! Everyone, look forward to it after you buy them. Of course it's a no!
あ、ごめんなさい、ごめんなさい。
Ah, sorry, sorry.
よし、よし、よし、戻って。まだ2枚もあるんで。お次はこちら！
Alright, alright, alright, go back. We still have two more cards left. Next is this!
ドーン！オープン！
Boom! Open!
なんと、あの作品とコラボ！？え？何、何？あの作品？
To our surprise, a collaboration with that series?! Huh? What, what? That series?
あの作品？どれだ？どれだ？ちょっと待って、これはマジで知らない。
That series? Which one is it? Which one? Wait, I seriously don't know about this one.
あの作品って何ですか？何だろう？何だろう？こちらをどうぞ。
What is "that series"? What could it be? Here you go.
サテーー
[Text: Now then...]
突然デハアルガ、
[Text: Though it is sudden,]
或ル秘密結社ノ話ヲシヨウ。
[Text: let's talk about a certain secret society.]
人間ハ、
[Text: Humans are...]
其ノ怪シイ集団ハ、
That suspicious group...
偶像――“アキドル”ナノダト云フ。
...they say they are idols.
ソシテ――
And...
正確ナ話ヲスルト 征服ショウトシテイルノハ エデンノ星ラシイ。
To tell the truth, what they are trying to conquer is seemingly the planet Eden.
タダ、ドウィウコトカ、交ハルハズノナキ世界ガ、
However, somehow, these worlds that were never meant to cross,
今回バカリハ 油断シテシマッタラシイ。
just this once, seem to have let their guard down.
交
Cross
秘密結社holoX × 物語シリーズ 其ノ零
Secret Society holoX x Monogatari Series: Part Zero
コラボ開催決定
Collaboration Confirmed
うわああ！ええ！？いいの！？え、やばい！
Whoa! What?! Is this okay? Oh my god, this is crazy!
いいんですか！？ え、やばすぎ！
Are they sure this is okay?! Wait, this is way too crazy!
え、めっちゃ大ニュースじゃんね！
Wait, this is massive news, right?!
ね、好き！え、やばすぎる！
Yes! I love it! This is too crazy!
どういうこと？でもさ… どっか行っちゃう！
What does this mean? But wait... She's wandering off!
どっか行っちゃう！ちょっと待って！
She's wandering off! Hold on a second!
ということで、ありがとうございました！
So, thank you so much!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
なんと！
And what's more...
まじで？え、怒られない？我輩…
Seriously? Wait, won't I get scolded? I...
怒られない怒られない！
No one's getting scolded!
怒られるとしたら、台本を読んでない子が怒られる！
If anyone gets scolded, it'll be the one who didn't read the script!
これ！早くタイトル言って！
This! Hurry up and read the title!
なんと！物語シリーズとのコラボが決定しました！
Unbelievably, our collaboration with the Monogatari Series has been confirmed!
どういうこと！？
What does this even mean?!
みんなも言ってる！
Everyone's saying it too!
詳細は順次発表されるようなので…
Details will be announced gradually, so...
え、我々も分かってない？
Wait, we don't even know either?
そうなんです。ホントに詳細が何も…
Exactly. We honestly have zero details...
分かってない！
We don't know!
え、どういうことですか？
Wait, what does that mean?
いや、ちょっと、うちらも焦ってるんですけど…
Well, we're actually panicking a bit too...
いいんですか？いいんですかって感じなんですけども。
Like, is this okay? Is this really allowed?
ちょっと、最後に一つ…
But anyway, we have one last thing...
あ、もう一個ある？
Oh, is there another one?
あるみたいなんで、そちらをいきましょう！
It looks like there is, so let's check it out!
もう一個見ないと行けないんだ！
We have to look at one more!
一旦動揺を、動揺を落ち着けて！みんな！落ち着いて！
First, calm down! Everyone, calm down!
我々が動揺してる間に、皆さん、この6つ目が何か…
While we are panicking, everyone, what do you think this sixth item is?
コメントで教えてください！
Please tell us in the comments!
何かな？コメント、コメント見に行こう！
What could it be? Let's look at the comments!
何だろうね？
I wonder what it is.
しのぶ？しのぶかな？
Shinobu? Could it be Shinobu?
最後の1つは皆さん何だと思いますか？
What do you all think the last one is?
なんとですね、まあ、ヒントを言うと…
Well, actually, if I give you a hint...
まあ、今年2曲作りましたよね？
We made two songs this year, right?
あ、作った作った！
Ah, we did!
全部で、holoXって何曲ありますか？
In total, how many songs does holoX have?
何曲？何曲だ？そうして…
How many? How many? And so...
え、あの、たくさん！覚えてないのか？
Uh, a lot! Do you not remember?
holoXが出してきた、企画を除きまして…
Excluding projects, holoX has released...
全部で7曲あります！
...seven songs in total!
7曲！すごい！多いね！
Seven songs! That's amazing! That's a lot!
え、ってことは？
Wait, which means...?
もしや？
Could it be...?
みんな分かってるかな？コメント欄分かってきたんじゃない？
Does everyone understand? The comments section seems to get it!
まだ？いや、あ、あ、あ、当たってる当たってる！
Not yet? Oh, they are getting it right!
ということで、気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、やっぱりあれでございます！6枚目オープン！
So, it seems some people have noticed, and yes, it is indeed that! Open the sixth card!
オープン！じゃん！
Open! Ta-da!
なんと！ファーストアルバムが出ます！
Unbelievably, our first album is coming out!
うわああ！やったー！嬉しい！
Whoa! Yay! I'm so happy!
ということで、ファーストアルバム『Secret ORDER』！
So, our first album "Secret ORDER"!
え、オーダー言っちゃった！大事故大事故！
Oh, she said "order"! A major accident!
Secret ORDERです！
It's Secret ORDER!
こちらの『Secret ORDER』は、holoXでの4年間をぎゅっと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております！
This "Secret ORDER" is an album packed with our four years in holoX!
我々のデビュー曲『ジョイリーペイント』はオリジナルバージョンに加えて、本作のために新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
Our debut song "Joyry Paint", in addition to the original version, also includes a newly rearranged version created just for this album!
おおー！そしてさらに、何かまだ未発表の楽曲も…
Oh! And furthermore, some as-yet-unreleased songs are...
ある？ない？
Are there? Or not?
なんか8とか9とか10とか11とか…
Like 8, or 9, 10, 11...
多すぎる！多すぎる！
That's too many!
ということでですね、通常盤になるんですけれども…あ、ちょっと上が見えないです…
So, regarding the regular edition... ah, wait, the top of the screen is cut off...
流れがね。すいません。通常盤には初回限定特典があります！
The timing. I'm sorry. The regular edition comes with a first-press limited bonus!
こちらでございますね。
Here it is.
各メンバーのソロバージョン、そしてジャケット4種類のうちランダムで1枚つきます！
It includes one random solo version cover out of four types, one for each member!
そしてこちらですね、4枚並べると、どうやら1枚絵になるとのことですよ！
And here, if you line up all four, they apparently form a single completed illustration!
おおー！すごーい！すごいつながりそうな顔してる！
Oh, amazing! Their faces look like they're definitely going to connect!
ラプラスの角が、刀の上にいる！
La+'s horn is right above the sword!
あ、本当だ！じゃあこれさ、並べないと！並べなきゃいけない！
Ah, you're right! So in that case, we have to line them up! You have to line them up!
そして！完全生産限定盤封入特典は、カッコよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが…
And! The complete production limited edition bonus for this cool album includes a holoX-style secret gimmick...
秘密の仕掛け？えー、我々も分かってないぞ！
A secret gimmick? Wait, we don't even know what it is!
隠されているとか！
Apparently, it's hidden!
なんだってー！？はい、ちょっと私たちも分からないのですが、この後22時から販売開始です！
What?! Yes, we don't really know either, but sales will start right after this at 10:00 PM!
22時から！ぜひぜひご予約お願いいたします！
From 10:00 PM! Please, please preorder yours!
ということで、めっちゃ告知盛りだくさんだったんですけど…
So, we had tons of announcements...
告知カードちゃんたちはこれで役目を終えて…きれいにバイバイ！
And these announcement cards have now served their purpose... clean say goodbye!
ぽよーん！いや、効果音を口で言い過ぎだな！
Boing! You're making too many vocal sound effects!
この3枚やばいだろ！ということで、ライブもラストパートでございます！
These three cards are crazy, right? And so, we've reached the final part of our live stream!
この後ですね、何やら、ちょっと、お知らせ？サプライズ？があるらしいですよ！
After this, apparently there's some kind of... announcement? Or surprise?
はい、最後までチャンネルはそのままでお願いいたします！
Yes, please keep watching until the very end!
いくじょ！みんな！
Let's go, everyone!
最後まで楽しんで！
Enjoy until the end!
行くぞー！行くぞー！イェーイ！
Here we go! Let's go! Yay!
おい！おい！おい！
Hey! Hey! Hey!
そこに跪け！
Kneel down right there!
はい、ピースですよ
Yes, peace!
現実逃避！
Escapism!
一刀両断！ 叩き切る！
With a single stroke! Slay them down!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし子らよ！
Oh, children lost in the endless cycle of rebirth!
漆黒の翼でいざなおう
Let me guide you with my pitch-black wings.
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社…
We, the rulers of the planet Eden, Secret Society...
holoX！
holoX!
テイクオフでござる！
Take off, de gozaru!
Woah woah woah...
反論 どうしようもないこの世界
Objecting to this world we can do nothing about,
どうして欲しい？
what do you want us to do?
不和か？
Is it discord?
終末告げる鐘が鳴る
The bell tolling the end is ringing.
わっぱっぱっと踊れ Sweet Sweet Time
Dance wildly in this sweet, sweet time,
Losing all of it Can we go Can we go Sing a song
気持ちいいことだけがすべて 落ちてゆく闇の底へ
Only the pleasant things are everything, falling to the bottom of the darkness.
甘い甘いメロディ ほらどうぞどうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
A sweet, sweet melody, come on this way, this way, towards the clapping hands.
もう人間でいられない
I can no longer remain human.
ほら
Look,
闇に染まれば
if you are dyed in darkness,
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish, I shall give you everything.
常識を破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense!
狂狂狂いたおせ 火をつけろ
Go absolutely mad, light the fire!
Rappappappaddabada
Rappappappa daddabada
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything completely!
Rappappappaddabada
Rappappappa daddabada
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
Woah woah woah...
悪のカリスマ 導くぞ神託さ
The charisma of evil, I will guide you with the oracle!
正義とか知らない 地ならしして誘い
I know nothing of justice, leveling the ground to invite you.
真面目に不真面目 電波の通う儀礼
Seriously playful, a ritual with electric waves,
望み求め願い叶え 世界征服！
Wishing, seeking, fulfilling desires, world domination!
わっぱっぱっと漂うエブリシング 歌おうぜ
Let's sing of everything drifting wildly,
退屈な世界へ バイバイバイ
and say bye-bye-bye to this boring world!
覚めることのない 夢を見せる
I'll show you a dream from which you'll never wake.
ほら お眠りなさい
Come, now fall asleep.
もっともっと 遠くへ ほらどうぞどうぞ 行きたいでしょう
Further and further away, come, please, please, you want to go, don't you?
もう止められない
I can't stop anymore.
ほら
Look,
悪に染まれば
if you are dyed in evil,
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望むもの give you すべて
I shall give you everything you desire.
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules!
狂狂回し尽くせ 世界をきつくきつく
Spin the world all around, tighter and tighter.
Rappappappaddabada
Rappappappa daddabada
すべてのまがいものよ
All of you imitations,
Rappappappaddabada
Rappappappa daddabada
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
ついに2周年！
Finally, our 2nd anniversary!
狂気の宴の始まりだ！
The feast of madness begins!
貴様ら、準備はいいか！
Are you ready, you bastards?
刮目せよ！
Feast your eyes!
holoX！ holoX！
holoX! holoX!
手を上げろ！ 手を上げろ！
Raise your hands! Raise your hands!
いろは！ いろは！
Iroha! Iroha!
叫ぶでござる！
Scream, de gozaru!
こより！ こより！
Koyori! Koyori!
踊って！ 踊って！
Dance! Dance!
世界を征服！ holoX！
Conquer the world! holoX!
世界を変えて！ holoX！
Change the world! holoX!
るい！ るい！
Lui! Lui!
もっと！ もっと！
More! More!
ラプラス！ ラプラス！
Laplus! Laplus!
最後は全員で！
Lastly, everyone together!
holoX！ holoX！
holoX! holoX!
世界を征服！ holoX！
Conquer the world! holoX!
世界を変えて！ holoX！
Change the world! holoX!
世界をこの手に！ holoX！
The world in our hands! holoX!
心を解き放って
Set your heart free,
ほらどうぞどうぞ 身を任せて
come, please, please, surrender yourself,
もう逃げられない
you can no longer escape.
ほら
Look,
闇に染まれば
if you are dyed in darkness,
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろう すべて
If you wish, I shall give you everything.
常識を破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense!
狂狂狂いたおせ 火をつけろ
Go absolutely mad, light the fire!
Rappappappaddabada
Rappappappa daddabada
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything completely!
Rappappappaddabada
Rappappappa daddabada
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you the secret.
Woah woah woah...
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社…
We are the rulers of the planet Eden, the secret society...
holoX！
holoX!
って、ごるぁ！
Wait, hey!
Let's go!
機は熟した！ 暁闇より現れし英霊たちよ
The time has come! Heroic spirits arising from the dawn darkness...
準備はいいか！
...are you ready?!
おーーー！
Yeah!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー
Lappappa LaPaLaPa Lappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Lappappa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
The night deepens, behold, darkness
能ある鷹は PONで隠す
A clever hawk hides its claws with PON
脳に従え エゴイスティック
Follow your brain, egoistically
のっと！ニンニン！！ サムライDJ参上！
Not nin-nin! Samurai DJ has arrived!
闇金しないけど
I don't do loan-sharking, but...
フルベッドでしょ
I'm betting it all, right?
征服すればOK
As long as we conquer it, it's OK!
切り裂く赤字 (シャキーン！ シャキーン！)
Cutting through the deficit (Clang! Clang!)
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
In the palm of evil, you'll want to dance
ほら君も 気付けば ノリノリです
Look, before you know it, you're grooving too
どうしようもない (Don't show, No min)
There's no helping it (Don't show, No min)
堕ちてく運命
A falling fate
ならしょうがない
Then it can't be helped
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now!
エクスと エクスと エクスと エクスが
Ecstas and Ecstas and Ecstas and Ecstas...
交差する真ん中で
intersect right in the center!
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト
Next, Next, Next, Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
The world has already begun!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
飛びな 飛びな 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Fly, fly, towards where the darkness calls
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
暗黒の エクスデス
Darkness Ecstas
混沌としたこの世界を、我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！ 皆の者、かかれ！
This chaotic world, we shall repaint it in our holoX colors! Everyone, charge!
Yes My Dark!!!
完璧漆黒∞ (アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ)
Perfect Pitch Black ∞ (Absolute Darkness Infinity)
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The planet Eden is in my hands!
魔眼ホークアイ！
Evil Eye Hawkeye!
お前もholoXerの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of holoXer!
コヨリウムボム！
Koyorium Bomb!
これで君も、コヨリにメロメロ～！
With this, you'll fall head over heels for Koyori!
疾風木枯らし斬り！
Gale Wintry Wind Slash!
一刀両断叩き斬る！
Splitting in two with a single slash!
どうしようもない (Don't show, No min)
There's no helping it (Don't show, No min)
堕ちてく運命
A falling fate
ならしょうがない
Then it can't be helped
もう全部 塗り替えよう
Let's repaint everything now!
刮目せよ！
Feast your eyes!
エクスと エクスと エクスと エクスが
Ecstas and Ecstas and Ecstas and Ecstas...
交差する真ん中で
intersect right in the center!
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト
Next, Next, Next, Next...
世界はもう 始まってる
The world has already begun!
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
媚びぬ 媚びぬ つまり最後
Unflinching, unflinching, meaning in the end...
(ウォッオッオ オーオーオー)
(Woah-oh-oh, oh-oh-oh)
笑うのは holoX です
the one who laughs last is holoX!
ラッパッパー LaPaLaPa ラッパッパー LaPaTa LaPaTa ラッパッパー
Lappappa LaPaLaPa Lappappa LaPaTa LaPaTa Lappappa
Yeah!
秘密結社holoX 一件の通知
[Notification: Secret Society holoX - 1 Message]
SECRET ORDER
機ハ熟シター
[The time has come...]
全テノ "holoXer" ヘ告グ
[An announcement to all "holoXers"...]
集ヘ、決戦ノ地
[Gather at the battleground...]
2026.4.29
[April 29, 2026]
PIA ARENA MM
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 1st MISSION
[Secret Society holoX Live 2026: 1st MISSION]
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
[Are you ready to take over the world?]
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
[The mad banquet begins...]
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
[#SSholoXWorldRepaintProject]
やったーーー！
We did it!
やったー！嬉しいー！
We did it! I'm so happy!
やったー！
Yes!
みんなも踊ってくれてる？
Is everyone dancing along too?
いかがでしたか？
How did you like it?
やばいね！
That was crazy!
早いよ、まだ早いから。
It's too early! We're not done yet.
やばいね。
It really is.
ということで、なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！
So, our live concert venue has actually been decided!
やったーーー！
Yay!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ファーストミッション！
First Mission!
ということで、みんなそれぞれね、感想と…
So, let's hear everyone's thoughts...
ライブに向けての抱負をお願いしたいと思います。
...and their aspirations for the live concert!
まずは、じゃあ私から
First, let's start with me.
決まったな
It's decided!
決まったね
We're doing it!
いや、めちゃくちゃね、あの、デビューの時から、ライブやりたいねって言ってて
Well, ever since our debut, we've always been saying how we wanted to do a live concert...
デビュー前から
...even before our debut.
それが、もうありがたいことにね...
And now, thankfully...
泣くな！泣くな！泣くのは早い！
Don't cry yet! It's too early to cry!
皆さんのご協力のおかげで、ホロクサーさんたちの応援のおかげで、叶いました！やったー！
Thanks to everyone's cooperation and the support of all the holoxers, it has finally come true! Yay!
やったー！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
えー、もう、ホロクスの皆で、当日は盛り上げたいと思いますので
We want to make the event super exciting with all of holoX...
ぜひ、みんな遊びに来てください！かっこいいホロクスを見に来てね！
...so please come and see us! Come see a cool side of holoX!
見に来てねー！
Come see us!
はい、ということで、続いては、じゃあ、こよ！
Alright, so next up is Koyori!
はい！えー、ま、今言ってた通り、みんなライブやりたいねって話もしてたし
Yes! Well, as she just said, we've all been talking about wanting to do a live show...
やっぱ、こよは一番忘れられない風景が、初めてのフェスで、ホロクスでやった時の
...and for me, the most unforgettable sight was during our first HoloFest together as holoX...
あの、ジョイフルペイントで会場がもう、わってなってくれたの、浴びた時
...when we performed Joyful Paint and the entire venue just went wild, bathing in that energy.
あれが、もうずっと忘れられないんで、やっぱり、その、今度はね
I can never forget that, so this time...
ホロクサーさんたちだけの会場、俺たちの会場で
...in a venue filled only with holoxers—our own venue...
やれるっていうのが
...being able to perform there...
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
...makes me incredibly happy!
できて、本当に、このやらせてくれることに、してくれた大人の皆さんにも
I'm so grateful to all the staff who made this happen...
あ、大人の皆さん、ありがとうございます！
...thank you, staff!
この4人のできる力を全て出して
We will give it everything these four can do...
そして歌とダンスもね、より一層力を込めてやっていきますので
...and put even more energy into our singing and dancing!
絶対現地、そして現地来られない人は映像でも絶対見に来てください！よろしくお願いします！
So please come to the venue, or if you can't make it, watch the stream! Thank you!
はい！いろは氏！
Yes! Iroha-shi!
みんな！生でござるたちの声が聞ける機会！
Everyone! This is your chance to hear our voices live!
ホロクスのこのハーモニーが聞ける機会！
Your chance to hear holoX's harmony!
ハーモニー、共鳴！俺たちの共鳴！
Harmony, resonance! Our resonance!
聞けちゃうござる！
You will get to hear it, gozaru!
はい！いや、もう本当にね、ホロクス、やっぱ、本当にみんな言ってるけどデビュー前からね
Yes! No, really, just as everyone has been saying, since before our debut...
現地ライブを、このメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので
...we've been saying we want to do a venue live with these members...
それがやっと叶ってね、でかい声出して、みんなで盛り上がれるのを、今か今かとね、楽しみにしております！
...so now that it's finally coming true, I'm eagerly looking forward to shouting loud and getting hyped together!
我々もね、4人とも、しっかり当日までレッスンや、
The four of us will also be doing lessons...
もうね、練習も含め、パフォーマンスも全部、色々みんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて、挑みますので、
...including practice, and thinking about so many ways to make the performance enjoyable for you all...
見ている皆さんも、ぜひ、全力で楽しみにして、そして当日は全力で楽しんでください！
...so everyone watching, please look forward to it with all your might, and enjoy it to the fullest on the day!
頑張ります！盛り上げる準備、出来てます！
We'll do our best! We're ready to get hyped!
じゃ、最後、総帥！総帥決めてくれ！
Now, finally, Leader! Leader, wrap it up!
よっちょ。毎回この最後をやるのやめてほしいんだよね
Yoccho. I wish you guys would stop making me go last every time.
ちょっと、みんな！ついに！
Wait, everyone! Finally!
ホロクスが…俺たちが…ライブ！！！
holoX... we... are doing a live concert!!!
ライブー！
A live!
もうみんなはさ、もうすごいライブやりたい、音楽大好き、みたいにずっと言ってたからさ
Since everyone has always been saying how much they want to do a live show and how much they love music...
俺は嬉しいよ
...I'm happy for you all.
いやもちろん、俺もやっぱりライブが一番楽しいから
No, of course. For me, live shows are the most fun too.
やっぱホロクスの活動ってなんかライブって感じじゃん
And holoX's activities feel like they're all about live performances, right?
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもホロクサーがばーって入るとこでできるのが嬉しいよな
So it makes me so happy that we can do this just as ourselves, and in a venue filled with holoxers.
嬉しいよね！熱いよ！熱い！
It really does! It's so hot!
俺たち本当に色んなことがあったけど、これからも本当に、4人いれば大丈夫だから
We've really been through a lot, but as long as the four of us are here, we'll be fine.
頑張ろう！
Let's do our best!
頑張るぞー！
We'll do our best!
速報です！トレンド1位ということで！
Breaking news! We are trending #1!
やったー！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
ここから4月29日までもう止まらねえので、トレンドに入れまくっててください！
We won't stop from here until April 29th, so please keep trending us!
はい！ということで改めて、秘密結社holoX 1st Live「1st MISSION」は4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
Alright! Once again, Secret Society holoX's 1st Live "1st MISSION" will be held on April 29th at PIA Arena MM!
やったー！空けとけ空けとけ！
Yay! Clear your schedules!
はい！諸々の詳細は後日発表予定とのことなので、皆さん続報を待てでござる！
Yes! Various details are scheduled to be announced at a later date, so please wait for further updates!
よろしく！よろしくおねがいします！
We're counting on you!
そして、そして！先程聞いていただきました新曲「叫乱エクス」
And also! The new song you just listened to, "Kyoran Ex"...
22時、22時10分よりですね、
Starting from 22:10,
MVをプレミア公開したいと思います！
we'll be premiering our music video!
イェーイ！ おお！
Yay! Awesome!
カッコいいね！
So cool!
そして、
And,
本日24時ですね、12月2日の0時に
at midnight tonight, 0:00 on December 2nd,
デジタルリリースが開始されますので、
it will be released digitally, so
ライブに向けてたくさん聴いてくれよな！
listen to it a lot in preparation for the live!
いや、もうコールできるとこいっぱいだからね！
There are so many parts where you can chant!
めちゃめちゃもう、もうライブのための曲！
It's totally a song made for live concerts!
エクス！ エクス！ エクス！ エクス！
X! X! X! X!
お前ら新曲いっぱい聴いて、
Everyone, listen to our new song a lot,
予習して、ライブ楽しみに待っててほしい！
prepare, and look forward to the live concert!
そして、アルバム「Secret Order」を…持って！
And also, get the album "Secret Order"!
持って？ 持って？
Get? Get?
奪われないように気をつけてね、持って、
Be careful not to get it stolen, and carry it,
ライブ来てね！
then come to the live!
持ってね、持ってね、
Carry it, carry it,
聴いて、予習してね！
listen and prepare!
アルバムは、えっと、22時から販売開始です！
The album sales start at 22:00!
もう1分で！ 買ってね！
In just one minute! Go buy it!
ホロックスのみんな！
Everyone in holoX!
うん、本当に2年間ありがとう！
Yes, thank you so much for these two years!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
えー、来年は、もう、
Next year, we will make it
ホロックスの、我々の年にしていくので、
holoX's, our year,
頑張ろうね！
so let's do our best!
3年目も、よろしくお願いします！
Please support us in our third year too!
よろしくお願いします！
Please support us!
じゃあ、みんな、
Alright, everyone,
せーので行くよ、
let's go on three.
せーの、
One, two,
バイバイ！
bye-bye!
解散！ 解散！
Disperse! Disperse!
やった！ やった！
We did it! We did it!
やったー！
Yay!
イェーイ！
バイバイ！
Bye-bye!